Guide to the Zelda Fichandler papers, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
- Zelda Fichandler papers
  - "A Doll's House", production material (Box 101, Folder 20)
  - "A Doll House", production script (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - "Domestic Issues", playbill (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - "Domino Courts", correspondence (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - "Don Juan" script (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - "Don Juan in Hell", script and production materials (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - "Don't Let it go to you Head", review and program (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - "Down by the river where waterlilies are disfigured everyday", playbill and notes (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - "Dracula", advertisement (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Women's National Democratic Club performance of "Alexis we Love You", script and program (Box 103)
  - "Audrey Wood", correspondence (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - "Elizabeth Woodman", casting info (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: William Woodman (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Worldnet USA theatre program information (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Mr. Garland Wright (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Lord and Lady Wright, British Ambassador to the US (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - program and order of events for Lord and Lady Wrights farwell tribute (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: The University of Wyoming (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Yale University (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - correspondence: Sidney Yates (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - correspondence: Rina Yerushalmi (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - young playwrights festival program 1987-1988 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - The Young Waterloo theatre (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - YWCA panel, Dec. 12, 1981 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - correspondence: Paul Zaloom (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - Mr. Zavadsky visit (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - correspondence: Joe Zeigler (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - correspondence: Peter Zeisler (Box 103, Folder 20)
  - correspondence: Joy Zinoman (Box 103, Folder 21)
  - remarks: Julliard School, League of Professional Theatre Training program, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - correspondence and notes on Julliard Presentation, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - speech:Theatre Communications Group, June 1983 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Speech: Theatre Communication Group, July 1983 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - statement for the Arena Stage Endownment Campaign, Sept. 1983 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - The New American Theatre and Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Announcement upon assuming the chair of the NYU theatre program (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - remarks: first rehearsal of "Three Sisters", Dec. 1983 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - remarks: Southeastern Theatre Conference, March 1984 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - statement by artistic director (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - NEA grant proposal, March 1984 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - "Women and Water", research (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - "Women and Water", master script (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - "Women and Water", final Production copy of script (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - "Women and Water", script (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - "Working", pre-production material (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - "The Workroom", playbill (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - "The World Goes Round", playbill (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - "The World of Ruth Draper", correspondence (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - "The World of Sholom Aleichem", program and press release (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - "The World's Greatest Play", correspondence (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - "Woyzeck", correspondence (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - "Woza Albert", playbill, research and reviews (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - "A Yard of Sun", correspondence (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - "The Year Boston Won the Pennant", correspondence and reviews (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - "Yossele Golem", program (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - "You Can't take it With You", reviews (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - "Wild Honey", playbill (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - "Wild Milk", script and reviews (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - "Emlyn Williams as Charles Dickens", reviews (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - "The Wind in the Willows", playbill (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - "Wine Untouched", playbill (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - "Winne the Pooh", correspondence (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - "The Winslow Boy", reviews (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - "Winters Tale", correspondence (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - "Within Two Shadows", correspondence (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - "We All Fall Down", production materials (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - "Wizard of ID", production materials (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - "Wizard of ID", scripts, book and cassette tape (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - "Women and Water", research (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - "You Can't Take it with You", production sch. (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - "You Know Al, He's a Funny Guy", reviews (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - "You Strike the Women, You Strike the Rock", correspondence (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - "You're too Tall, But Come Back in two weeks", playbill and correspondence (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - "Your own Thing", reviews (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - "Zephyr", playbill (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - "Zero", correspondence (Box 106, Folder 20)
  - "Zoot Suit", playbill (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - correspondence with the District of Columbia regarding the Hippodrome theatre, Feb. 1950 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Report to stockholders, June 1955 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Speech: to the cultural development committee, Washington Board of Trade, Nov. 1955 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - report to stockholders, March 1957 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - report to stockholders, June 1957 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - stockholders meeting, June 1958 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Ford Foundation, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - report: A Permanent Classical Repertory Theatre in the Nation's Capital, June 1959 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Report to IRS; statement of activities and purpose of Washington Drama Society Inc., June 1959 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - correspondence to stockholders, October 1959 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - remarks: stockholders, October 1959 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - fundraising speech, November 1959 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - correspondence; 20th century fund, Nov. 1959 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - speech: Banard Club, Nov. 1959 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - speech: Harvard Business School Club, Dec. 1959 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - speech: WGMS, Dec. 1959 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - pamphlet: Arena Stage 1959 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - pamphlet: Arena Stage, 1960 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - press conference: design of new Arena Stage, 1960 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - speech: unknown (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - speech: Junior League of Washington, April 1960 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - Speech: Chicago (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - remarks: meeting of the Washington Drama Society, June 1960 (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - speech: at the groundbreaking, Oct. 1960 (Box 107, Folder 23)
  - remarks: meeting of Washington Drama Society, June 1961 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - transcript: Pat Hayes Program, WGMS - Aug. 20, 1961 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - speech: Dedication Oct. 1961 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - remarks: dedication and housewarming of Arenas new stage, Oct. 1961 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Notes on the Building by HArry Weese (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Information on the new building (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - artical: Arena Stage and its Audience, May 1962 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Speech: AD Club, June 5, 1962 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - article: The Art of Drama, July, 1962 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - article: operation santa, Nov. 1962 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - speech: The Board of Standards and Planning for the Living Theatre, March 3, 1963 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - speech: American Society of Newspaper Editors, April 19, 1963 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - panel discussion: Seminar on Theatre, May 11, 1963 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - remarks: women's newspaper club, April 23, 1964 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - speech: 15th anniversary dinner (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - article: A Place for Seeing (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - article: The Development of the Repertory Actor, Feb. 18, 1965 (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - remarks: to the Company April 15, 1965 (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - correspondence: travel to greece, July 4, 1965 (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - remarks: panel on the open stage, International Theatre Institute Conference, June 1967 (Box 108, Folder 20)
  - remarks: Conference on Theatre Education and Development, June 18, 1967 (Box 108, Folder 21)
  - article: To Build a Theatre, May/June 1967 (Box 108, Folder 22)
  - correspondence: to Arena Stage Friends, 1967 (Box 108, Folder 23)
  - speech: AETA panel; future of the resident professional theatre in America, Aug. 1967 (Box 108, Folder 24)
  - newsclipping: Minneapolis Tribune, Oct. 1967 (Box 108, Folder 25)
  - report: Arena Stage Training program- Feb. 16, 1968 (Box 108, Folder 26)
  - paper: Towards a Deepening Aesthetic, March 1968 (Box 108, Folder 27)
  - paper: Specifics of the Plan (Box 108, Folder 27)
  - misc. paper (Box 108, Folder 28)
  - newsclippings: Washington Star, June 30, 1968 (Box 108, Folder 29)
  - Misc. correspondence, Feb. 1968 - July 1968 (Box 108, Folder 30)
  - research and news clippings on African Americans (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Arena Stage brochure, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings: Arena Stage extension ground breaking, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Speech: on turning 40 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - speech: ground breaking, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: regrading the 1968 extension (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - correspondence and magazine: Saturday Review, Dec. 1969 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - speech and information: Montgomery College, May 14, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - personal notes (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Washington Post article: July 5, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - misc. notes, articles and information (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - International Theatre Institute, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - tour of Kreeger Theatre, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - architectureal notes, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - notes on the Kreeger Theatre, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - speech and notes: South Caroline Theatre Association, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - University of Texas teaching, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - informaiton on Texas lecture series (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - University of Texas - Seminar Lecture I (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - University of Texas - Seminar Lecture II (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - University of Texas - Seminar Lecture III (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - University of Texas - Seminar Lecture, March 29, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - University of Texas - Seminar Lecture V (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Saturday Review, March 27, 1971 (2) (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - article: Open Secrets (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - speech: International Club, Feb. 8, 1972 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Feb. 14, 1972 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - speech: Women's Auxiliary of Phi Delta Epsilon Medical Fraternity (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Morgan Jones Award, May 1972 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - speech: Carnegie Mellon, Oct. 1972 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - speech: Boston University. Nov. 1972 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: John Housemann (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - correspondence/research/speech: Boston University (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - producer seminar: Brooklyn College, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - chronology of Arena Stage for Tour of Soviet Union (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - speech: Women's National Democratic Club, Nov. 1973 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - misc. speech and notes (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - article: United States Advisory Commission (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - National Press Club Award and Speech, Nov. 1973 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Speech: Arena Stage /TV, Feb. 1974 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - research materials: Television and Drama (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - research material- television and drama (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - "Born Guilty", research (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - "Born Guilty", revised script (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - "Born Guilty", Script revision (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - "Born Guilty", correspondence and research (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - "Born Guilty", correspondence and research (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - "Born Guilty", notes (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - "Born Guilty", newsclippings (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - "Born Guilty", research items (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - "Born Guilty", correspondence (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - "Born Guilty", press releases and casting information (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - "The Latent Heterosexual", correspondence (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - "Lear", correspondence (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - "The Learned Ladies", playbill (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - "Lemon Sky", reviews and correspondence (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - "Leonardo", treatment and notes (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - "L'Atelier", playbills (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - "Leonce and Lena", script, reviews, research, misc. items (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - "A Long Time A Comin'", playbill, correspondence, reviews (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - "Les Blancs", correspondence (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - "Les Blancs", lit. Material (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - "Les Liaisons Dangreuse", playbills and reviews (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - "A Lesson from Aloes", script, playbills (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - "Letters Home", correspondence and flyer (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - "A Lie of the Mind", playbill, reviews, correspondence (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - "Lie of the Mind", tour notes (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - "A Life", playbill, reviews (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - "Life Class", playbill and correspondence (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - "Life And Limb", review (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - "Life is a Dream", press release (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - "Light up the Sky", playbill, reviews, correspondence (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - "Lillian", playbill (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - "The Lion in Winter", playbill (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - "Liberation of Skopje", press materials (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - "Little Johnny Jones", playbill (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - "Littel Murders", playbill, correspondence, reviews (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - "Little Theatre of the Deaf", playbill, correspondence (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - "Little Theatre of the Deaf", reviews (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - "A little Wine with Lunch", correspondence (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - "Livin' Dolls", playbill (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - "Living at Home", stage managers reports, correspondence (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - "Lolita", reviews, playbills (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - "London Assurance", playbill and reviews (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - "Lonesome Train/Hard Travelin", correspondence (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - "Long Christmas Dinner", reviews (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night", book and production materials (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - "A Long Time Comin", reviews, script, correspondence (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - "A Look at the Fifties", script, stage managers reports, reviews, correspondenc and research (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - "The Long Journey of Poppie Nongena", review (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - "Look Back in Anger", correspondence (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - "Loose Ends", script (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - "Loot", reviews and playbill (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - "Lord Alfred's Lover", correspondence (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - "Los Alamos Atomic Bombers", script, reviews, research, correspondence (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - "Lost in the Stars", playbill (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - "Iphigenia", playbill (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - "Iphigenia in Aulis", playbill (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - "Isadora Duncan Sleeps with the Russian Navy", correspondence (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - "Isn't it Romantic", playbill, reviews, research (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - "It's the Truth", misc. materials (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - "Jaques Brel is Alive and Well and Living in Paris", playbills (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - "Jerome Kern Goes to Hollywood", playbills (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - "Jerry's Girls", articles (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - "Jesses' Land", playbill (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - "Jesus Christ Superstar", playbill (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - "Joan of Lorraine", playbill (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - "Joe Egg", playbill (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - "Joe Turner Come to Gone", study guide, playbill, research (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - "Joe Turner", literature materials (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - "John Brown's Body", correspondence (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - "Journey's End", playbill and review (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - "The Journey of the Fifth Horse", correspondence (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - "Journey to Jefferson", playbill (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - "Judevine", program, cast list, research (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Julius Caesar", stage reports, research, correspondence (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - "Jumpo at the Sun", production materials (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - "Jumpers", reviews and correspondence (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - "June Moon", playbill and correspondence (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - "Juno and the Paycock", playbill, reviews and research (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - K-2", script and photos (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - "K-2", reviews and articles (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - "K-2", reviews and correspondence (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - "Kafka's Dick", correspondence (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - "The Karl Marx Play", reviews (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - "The Kathy and Mo Show", playbill (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - "Kean", script, correspondence, reviews (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - "Kennedy's Children", playbill, research, other info (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - "Kiss of the Spider Woman", reviews and playbill (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - "Kitchen Church and Kids", correspondence (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - "THe Knight of the Last Half Hour", press release and correspondence (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - "Knights of the Round Table", playbill (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - "Knickle", press item (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - "A Kurt Weill Cabaret", playbill and review (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - "Ladies Tailor", notes (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - "The Lady from Dubuque", playbill (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - "Ladyhouse Blues", review (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - "Lamp at Midnight", correspondence (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - "Lampost Reunion", playbill (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - "Landscape of the Body", program (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - "La Ronde", review (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - "The Last Anylysis", correspondence (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - "Preston Jones", stage reports, reviews, correspondence (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - "The Last Street Play", program and review (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - "Last Summer in Chulimsk", program and review (Box 118, Folder 25)
  - "The Late Great Ladies of Blue Jazz", reviews (Box 118, Folder 26)
  - "Orkeny Play", production research (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - "The Screens", playbill and programs (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - "Scribes", playbill (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - "Scuba Duba", playbill (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - "The Sea", correspondence, reviews, playbills (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - "The Seagull", playbill and notes (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - "The Seagull", press release, playbill, reviews (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - "Shakespeares's Cabaret", review and audio cassette (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - "The Sea Gull", correspondence and reviews (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - "O'Neill's Sea Plays", reviews (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - "Season's Greetings", playbill (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - "The Second Greatest Crime of the Century", correspondence (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - "The Secret Place", correspondence (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - "See How They Run", review (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - "Semmelweiss", playbill (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - "Separations", correspondence (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - "Serenading Louie", review (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - "Serjeant Musgrave's Dance", playbill (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - "The Servant of Two Masters", brochure (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - "Sexual Perversity in Chicago and Duck Variations", program (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - "The Shadow Box", correspondence (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - "playbill" (Box 119, Folder 22)
  - "Shaft of Love", script and correspondence (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - "Shaw Says", script (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - "Shear Madness", playbills and reviews (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - "Sheba", correspondence (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - "Sherlock Holmes", playbill (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - "She Stoops to Conquer", playbills and reviews (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - "The Shortchanged Review", correspondence and reviews (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - "Short Eyes", program and reviews (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - "Shrivings", correspondence (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - "The Sign in Sidney Brustein's Window", correspondence, reviews, cast list, playbill (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - "Side by Side", playbill (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - "Singers", stage report and audience response (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - "The Silver Tassel", review (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - "The Sing Ling Circus", correspondence (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - "The Sirens", correspondence (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - "Sister Mary Ignatius Explains it all for You", misc. notes (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - "Sister Carrie", correspondence (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - "Six Character in Seach of an Author", notes and playbill (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - "Six Character in Seach of an Author", script (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - "Six Character in Seach of an Author", correspondence and reviews (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - "Six Character in Seach of an Author", notes, reviews and script (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - "Six Character in Seach of an Author", script with notes (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - "Six Character in Seach of an Author", script (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - misc. correspondence on plays, 1962-1963 season (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - correspondence on plays, 1962-1963 season (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - correspondence on plays, 1963-1964 season (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - correspondence on plays, 1963-1964 season (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - "Brosbure", production notes, 1963-1964 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - correspondence on plays, 1963-1964 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - blurbs on the plays of teh 1963-1964 season (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - correspondence, 1964-1965 season (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - information on plays, 1964 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - cover sheets to plays, 1964-1965 season (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - notes on plays under review (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - notes on plays under consideration (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - notes, reviews and information on misc. plays (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - workshop productions (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - reviews of potential plays (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - INCE - The Egg (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - notes on potential plays (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - press surrounding 30th anniversary season (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Ford Foundation (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - contracts - Actors and Directors (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - casting notes, 1967 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - cast breakdowns (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Anta Material (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - major grants awarded: 1959-1974 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - ANTA - ATNA materials (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - list of actors (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - 1965-1966 season brochure (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - 1965-1966 season schedule (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - 1965-1966 season material (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - 1965-1966 season correspondence (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - 1965-1966 production lists (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - 1966-1967 correspondece (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: ANTA (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: 1958-1959 season (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: 1960-1961 season (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: 1961-1962 season (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: 1961-1962 season (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: 1961-1962 season (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: 1962-1963 season (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Ernest J. Simmons (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - press releases from ACT, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Ed Winner (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - audience questionnaires (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Arnold Weinstein (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - proofs from the Washington Post (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - "Wise Words of Philosophy" (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Zel's Speeches (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: August Heckscher (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - American Negro Theatre (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - grants: playwrights (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - floor plan for the new building (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - playwright in residence: Conrad Bromberg (Box 130, Folder 2)